<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Odev3</string>
    <string name="computerEngineer">Computer Engineer</string>
    <string name="mobileApplicationDeveloper">Mobile Application Developer</string>
    <string name="aboutMe">About Me</string>
    <string name="aboutMeText">When I discovered that I wanted to develop my life in the fields of Mobile Programming, Mobile GameProgramming and Artificial Intelligence, I took the first step by choosing these fields as elective courses inmy school education. The concrete results I have seen in the face of my efforts to research and develophave helped me take steps that will take me further. I spend most of my time researching, training and,most importantly, developing a project in the areas I want to improve.</string>
    <string name="experience">Experience</string>
    <string name="experienceText">1 - Leader Technology Development Eng.Const.Ind. and Trade Ltd. Co. (LTG)\n\nIntern \n\nInternship in the RandD department of LTG Company for 25 working days. Developed the input-form screenof a project using the MFC library in C ++ language in Visual Studio Community 2019 softwaredevelopment environment.\n\n2 - Eskişehir Metropolitan Municipality - Information Technology Department - SoftwareDevelopment\n\nIntern\n\nA demo mobile application was developed to show the bus schedules and times of Eskisehir province. Aseparate mobile application was developed for the authorization system of this application. The databaseof both applications was developed with MySQL, the interface with PHP and the mobile part with JAVA.</string>
    <string name="education">Education</string>
    <string name="educationText">Duzce University        I graduated in Computer Engineering.\n\nGPA 3,33\n\n2019\nDuzce University        I successfully completed the optional English preparatory program at B1 level.</string>
    <string name="project">Project</string>
    <string name="projectText">An Application Of Facial Expression Recognition Based On Deep Learning\n\nAs an undergraduate thesis assignment, training was done in Google Colaboratory using FER2013 datasetand Transfer Learning (TL). The training was converted into TensorFlow Lite and used in a mobileapplication written in JAVA. From all the photos in the user\'s gallery, facial ones were classified by emotionanalysis. With this application, users can easily see the photos of which emotional states they want to view.SQLite and Firebase were used as database.\n\nMobile English Development App for Children\n\nA mobile application was developed that teaches animals and numbers at the beginner level, and also hasa quiz stage where the quiz results are kept in the scoreboard to increase children\'s motivation to learnEnglish. With this application, it was made easier for them to learn English at the beginner level and totranslate. Firebase was used as a database.\n\nHospital Automation with Layered Architecture\n\nAn automation project was developed for the processes in a hospital in C# language with layeredarchitecture using .NET Framework and MSSQL. With this project, patient records, reports and manyprocesses in the hospital were turned into a desktop program.</string>
    <string name="certificate">Certificate</string>
    <string name="certificateText">TRAI x DBB Artificial Intelligence Bootcamp 2021 – 2021\n\nBahçeşehir, Düzce and Başkent Universities IEEE Clubs, Google DSC Düzce Club and Turkey ArtificialIntelligence Initiative in cooperation with the 30-hour artificial intelligence camp I was entitled to receive acertificate of participation. With this camp, I was entitled to receive certificates of participation in the fieldsof Artificial Intelligence in Automation, Artificial Intelligence in Defense Industry, Artificial Intelligence inVoice Assistants, Artificial Intelligence in Law and Artificial Intelligence in Quality Control.</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="languageText">Turkish : Mother Tongue\nEnglish : Intermediate</string>
    <string name="skills">Skills</string>
    <string name="skillsText">•Android Studio    •JAVA     •C#     •Python   •SQL</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
</resources>